You thought you broke me?
Nah, pardon.
You just uncaged the psycho!
You wanted barbie should have treated her right, now you got Harley on a coke binge night
I'm the queen of fuck, who dressed in fishnets black
Got revenge in my purse mixed with lipstick and straps
Everywhere I spit got glitter on the blade
Pretty little nightmare that your motherfuckers made
You killed the soft side
Congratulations clown
Now the sweet little angel burns the whole town down
You wanted old me, dig up the grave
That bitch ain't breathing, she couldn't be safe!
You found your bad habit, your favorite mistake
Psycho juggalette with a smile so fake
Black beauty with a murder
With a blood red Barbie with a razor edge
Grinny, you created this
The gang's dancing through the wreckage while I lose
Crazy bitch, energy loud and proud
The tap your mama wants you not to bring around
Pretty doesn't mean weak, that's where you're fucked up
I break your ego with a smile and a strut
Tops like online and free space to face
Till I laugh real slow while I step in your space
Active, every bridge burn became another classic
Now my voice hit hard like a shotgun
Kissing every fake friend ended up on my hit list
Crying till the tears dry up and the demons start smiling
Now I'm outside and pigtails and rage
Like Harley Quinn has paid from Arkham
I'm your bad psycho juggalette
With a smile so fake
Black heart beauty with a murk
Head old fingers up
Things begin, ever see a girl smile
Right before she snaps
See y'all kept puttin' to the sweep when writein' how I danced through pain like it ain't forgotten
Mascara tears mixed with gasoline, beauty queen gone, full murder scene
I ain't chasing close to I chase and revenge, got my platform boots and your throat again
And every fake I care, that came out your mouth, sounded like another reason to burn shit down
Slow motion, through the flames I made, bubble gum psycho
It ain't gonna run scared when the fun cubes say sharp tongues out of my hide
I hit em blades inside, so by the time I click spit your ego die
I just had a really good time though I was at uh Mr. Extendo this chat and Ghost was up there too.
I think he's still up there. I mean it's like but uh he looked like he's falling asleep and
I want to talk about some things. How's everybody? I mean there's uh how do I start? I mean it's like
you know what's happening to me and which is like whatever this manifestation of some
Nightmare imposed by some other nightmare that's trying to blame it on me at their fingerprints all over it
they will be blamed and
Rightly so
I just don't understand
It's like if there is like if there was if I was like the littlest bit of a
Any of these things I'm called. I'm called a lot of things by that person
Who I was probably great friends with like about a week and a half ago
Think about it, right? I don't it doesn't make sense for someone to change so much overnight
unless
Maybe there's an arched demon involved. I don't know
But anyway, I feel
I feel
And this person will say all these things like I dull this
No
They're honest. They're honest
I never
Did anything to them except love
But they want to do this. It must be some other kind of
Reason or trauma. I mean, it's I don't know. It's like sad to me at this point sad. The really sad thing is now
Going after people. Well, here's the sad thing is I went to a few people and I said, hey
This is going on
Like basically, what do you think? What do you think, you know?
But what's happening?
Yeah, flip flopping is sweet. Yeah, now she's gone after Paige. Yeah
She she did a show and she's like pages. I mean it was really confusing. She's like pages
luring men
That she meets in my chat or something or and then she's in this in page. She's saying page is a trans
So I know like nobody really cared like if anything happens to me, but I know people
Care about her and so and it's like she's really she is she doesn't even has nothing to do with any of it
There's nothing all it's either try try to provoke
or something like that, but I'm really confused about it.
And, you know, I just have to like, but I have to,
here's what I'll do.
I'm gonna just be, I will be defending,
I'll be helping, and there for the first thing, you know?
Even if like not many people care about me,
I know because people get scared and stuff like that.
Listen, there's nothing to fear except fear itself, really.
And sometimes even the scariest most intimidating adversary can be like a little pussycat at the end of it
But all I can say is that the person
must be
Disturbed or something. I don't I don't know
I'm not gonna say I'm not gonna say the name, you know that there's an increase
there's these things of the Furies right the Greek Furies and they would be like nemesis is one of them and and you never
Felt fear you can't relate. Well, it's good, but you know what fear is actually like if you don't feel fear
Then you're at a disadvantage because there are some things that are
Dangerous and so fear is something kind of telling you watch out
My problem is I don't feel fear either and so I'm walking right into the lion's den with people and then it's like, you know, I
Just have like a little bit of a well, you know, Daniel survived the lion's den
So and so did I
But not everyone's Daniel and not everyone's me and not everyone's
This and this we have somebody that's out just you know talk about predatory and
Twisted and I'm just I'm actually like afraid. I mean not afraid of like human beings can like do this
That's be something more
more than
Just human
Could it be an alien could it be a demon?
Could it be both an alien demon put an alien demon vampire that knows witchcraft?
Well, I don't know. There's a lot of scary things in this world. I've survived this long, right? I've survived this long
Lola, oh my lord. Oh, you're so sweet
I know and you know what I can have a sharp tongue when I get offended and it's like maybe I've had a sharp tongue about some things
but it's like
This is like this is like beyond anything I've ever seen any
Anybody go through I mean it's like I've never seen it's like especially like public and then and then it's like and and celebrated oh
cats don't bite
Celebrated actually like that's the saddest part. There's people sitting around like oh yay
you know I
Know like it's like it's like let me see or either have hate watchers or they're just people that aren't talking or something
They just explain something to you. Don't be afraid to talk in my chat. Don't be afraid
it's fear is this tactic but it's like really this person this person is harmless but the problem is
that they're trying to what they say is something like oh you're going to be held accountable
countable by the worst of the worst now first of all why would i want to be held accountable by
the worst of the worst and second of all what gives the worst of the worst the right to judge
and serve justice upon me why is it the worst of the worst
just to punish and are you some kind of nightmare being like I don't understand
because it's like I wow talk about I mean I thought I was on the pedestal you are
but the thing is it's like it is it is confusing especially like you know
Bink basically is just like the person trying to learn every insecurity or every like the little thing and then like or every
Even good things and then like throw everything back, but if they could just like rewind a little bit watch you can watch
Watch how you can watch how they just change like the chameleon like like the moon. I don't even know
Obviously that two years apart that we're born is like some kind of big
It's a big difference. No, we have a guest
We have a guest, we have a ghost.
Ghosty.
Uh, train's passing, give me one minute.
My boy. Yeah, of course. What do you mean boy? Yeah, well give him I told him that like three times
But give him some if it's like you can't do that show on computers
Like if you're gonna put a link out make sure that people that are on the phone
I know I know
I don't know why I didn't work for me, but I don't know what I'll help figure it out if people were wrong, but uh,
Let him get some sleep in your school. How are you? Oh, Lola?
Did you have a good day? It was fun. There was a really cute guy in that last chat. He had a jester mask on. It was awesome
It was awesome. And I think that lady was nice too. She was pretty cool
But anyway, what I really want to say is like I would never I don't go after people that don't
He didn't do anything to me. I was just talking shit about his wings, but other than that I had a good time. I like big fat guys
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. No, no, I mean, I say, you know, oh, I'll say I'll say both sizes
But yeah, I mean, you know pages being attacked now. You heard that our page
Go see. I just told you a train's going boy. I have to meet up. I sure want to hear the fucking train
I want to hear the train whistle
No, I don't fuck it. Let's run it.
Well, nobody's worried about Paige, but what about me?
I've been attacked for like four months now.
It's fine, but Paige doesn't even, isn't even involved.
And it's like this one person's attacking that.
And it's like this person.
Well, here's the thing.
You wouldn't be saying that you're white knighting
because you've seen all stuff.
She wouldn't learn how to defend herself.
You wouldn't be saying nothing.
I'm not white knighting.
Here's what I'm going to do though.
It's like, because I would...
Did I have a white knight?
Did I have anybody that's...
Yeah, his name's Ghost.
You never said anything to her?
I don't know what's going on right now ghost. You know what's going on? I have no idea. Okay. What's backstage? Hold on a second
By the way, the train's wrong
I can't believe that was such a difference like if you don't post your link on a computer versus a phone that that
Trick me and all out earlier. Check out the back chat. I'm not you
You want me to read out louder just me know just read it yourself. Yeah, I don't agree with any of that
Yeah at all
Right, and I think if what can I can I can I talk about a little bit if you don't
Yeah, I think if you can I say the B word? Yeah
I think a few dogs that you're the you're the worst person ever you should never ever ever dogs
What's the point of that?
The only way I can logically look at it is you're trying to hurt someone right?
That's the only way you're doing it. Yeah, you're trying to hurt you're trying to and when I say hurt
I mean literally physically or
Emotionally like you're literally trying to hurt somebody right and it's not even just you're not up here
You're not up here debating
You know, I've heard talking, you know, you're literally trying to physically hurt someone when I say physically, meaning like, you know, a person like you, so like, you know, you get a DDT, like death threats on your panel by a lot of people.
Yeah, so if I would dox you, therefore I'd be like, well, here are people, here's where he lives at. I don't believe in that. If you're going to have a disagreement, I don't get along with a lot of people and I don't fucking dox them. And you know that.
Yeah
Remember I've been I was bullied and giving all these copyright strikes and you know harass and all these doorknocks and stuff remember that
Yeah, you know, you know, well, you know who I said was responsible for that, right?
We thought you were the same person, right
Oh, you thought about Tony like three years ago. Yeah. Well, that was three years ago
Do you know he was doing it up until recently? He was just indicted on me. I mean you thought I was told me three years ago
I oh, yeah, that was last year. But yeah, yeah, you know that those years
You know that he's not like the yeah, but by the way, can I say one thing though?
Go ahead. I won't lie. I used to hate on you, but I didn't hear him talk. He does sound like me. I'm not gonna lie
His voice does sound like me.
Yeah.
Well, I don't blame you on that.
I don't blame you on the same area, kind of.
I mean, I think he's around that area, but um.
Dude, I haven't turned it for years, but his voice did sound like me.
Right.
But he doesn't say you're heard, or in a real way, or commission.
So here's the thing.
I want to tell you the deal.
I want to tell you the deal about him.
So there's this, like, little group of them.
It's like a discord.
Can you send her your link?
Send her your link?
I got you or send me your link and I'll send it to you or send her your link
You know I'm sending it to you right now. Hold on
No, her not me
There's a group. Let's say some kind of gang on YouTube right there's a YouTube guy. Wait that guy called you an F word
Yeah, but I like it. So it's okay. Well, you should I mean free speech, you know, like
They're talking nonsense. Let's take us some those unless they got some logic behind that point you killed my boy
That's word. We don't care. I don't care. I mean seriously. No, I'm like the I'm like those laid-back cool person
And I don't get offended and shit like that and you know
But yeah, there's some there's some things you don't mess with about somebody you don't mess with somebody
Family damn
Family like publicly like it and bring people that are in
Family into it. I don't know. I don't know. Just looking insane. Okay. Listen. Yeah
Nice there's nothing wrong. There's something seriously wrong and then so I showed this tweet where the person actually says
Oh, yeah
I'm gonna go after families and I'll be your manifestation of people going after your loved ones and then they'll blame you
That's what that was her tweet. I didn't say it was like you said it was a tweet
It was a tweet she made some time in her life, right?
Yeah
Right, so she has a whole episode. Oh my god. Oh your daughter of Mott. Oh, that's awesome. Mayer kafa kalish ma I like it
And then she goes out your page and then she go but it's like the whole thing is if you uh
I'm sorry
I'm just saying I'm like it's like it's like and then I would like would love for somebody to I mean
I have a few people that you know
We're talking and stuff like that and and are like, you know in shock, but
Other people that I think would be maybe like
Yeah, it does but yeah other people I think would be like you know at least say I'm not looking for any help or anything
I'm looking for
understanding and like you know compassion or something like that and
I'm getting kind of just shut down and like say oh I
You know or it's like my fault, and I mean it's like not even that
It's really kind of shit kind of sad, and I'm like well
This is like how we this is what people are getting away with now
It's like it's like nobody really cares and it's like do you understand this how like I just wrong it is
I don't know. I don't know but I mean you get it. I know but
You know
Shitting on me here like literally anything I say like I have to do it for the next month
You know what's a perfect example of his hurt people hurt people because this happened to this person and she didn't like it
She didn't like what happened to her family
But I think just like the the Tony person
They're hurt and then they have to hurt other people now. I think we have a guest. Hold on. I'm gonna take it
Hi. Yeah, you can hey there. There you go. I love his avatar
Did you make that for him, too? Or he made it go ghost you made that avatar. I like it actually
Thank you. Who made was this that it was a New York guy. Who was it?
Might have been one of mine. I'm not sure.
And that was a New York guy that made it for me.
Okay. Yeah, I guess.
He made mine and I like it too.
I like yours and I like mine with the Pekingese
and the volcano in the back.
Yeah.
I remember when you said you said Pekingese
and you said something about Hawaii
and then I said a volcano.
I know. I love it. It's beautiful.
That's why I love it.
And you made it in different colors too.
I love it so I can change it out.
Thank you, you know, I love the art stuff that you do like the videos the AI stuff the music
I like I like that stuff. That's what you should do more of you know
It's it's the screw this drama and shit that's going on though
You know because there's a lot of evil people out there and you know what I'm doing real life
I'm very close to my family. You know what my brother and sister did
I'm gonna show you a picture. They brought me they bought me for my birthday a 65 inch TV at the top of the line
It's real. I don't know what he's he's into the TV suspects or whatever they call it
And it's expensive and he wanted me to give me to get an 80 inch and and I said no
I don't like it big. I like like a 50 inch or you know or 40 or whatever. You don't like it big
No, I mean, I mean, I don't like a huge screen, you know, I'm talking about the screen
I just like I don't like the movie time on the theater
Also, it's got a beautiful soundbar and it's it's worth
2000 and he got a deal for it and he he brought over a
Professional installer and they put it all up with no wiring or anything
and you know they got me the laptop too the real super fast gaming laptop it's got extra hard drive it's super fast and it's all wire especially with wireless because I got the blue stream what do you call it it's it's a oh my god it's it's wonderful it's expensive though but they brought me all that and now you know I download all these new movies you know from the
And it's all wireless, and I don't even have to use a USB or a cord.
I don't have to use a cord or anything to put it on the TV.
It just picks it up wireless on the TV.
It's super nice. I love it.
And yeah, and clumsy saying, you're not close to your family.
I'm very close to them because they were even texting me and I mean, they work.
We're very close, you know, me and my siblings, our parents are gone.
And one of them left me a message like a whispering
come kill your parents. Yeah. Like what? You know, my parents been dead. You know,
but I'm done with that. That's why I just stay with the positive stuff. Um, you know,
psyche just because I'm trying to do that and I hate people trying to be in my ear that this
is person saying this or do whatever. I'm not going at anybody. The only thing I do is react
Why I don't know if it's your parents fall or maybe your grandparents. When do you become so beautiful?
Are you Tommy see and then they take it they keep using an old fat pick from 2016, you know, and you've seen me psyche
You know and I'm saying if you said you expected to see a six hundred pound
Yeah
Elderly
Yeah, you were gonna see an old lady that was six hundred pounds. I don't even look my age
Don't remind me of lies
Well, there's a big is beautiful too, but you know what like she looked like lice. Oh, this is only 30 times over
Yeah, no, I'm kind of under so the doctor is getting on my case and I really have to keep up with the water
Can you go I know you're under and I really appreciate it. Can you under me? Oh come on?
And I didn't I didn't even have makeup on when I when psyche saw me the one you saw
That's me came up with makeup. You know, that's that was somebody
But it's crazy you don't fucking hate it. Well, let's talk about like, you know, there's I had to get I had this
You know this person that we knew on this like a you know
This tells his name is initiatives are be key, but he's like gone off gone off on both of us and you know
We were a CM we were we were really like they're
Almost in a supportive like you know or at least like trying to see the best and this like and then we get turned on and then
It's like when then other people turn on us
And then it just seems like, it's like, wow,
it's like, this is how kindness is repaid sometimes,
you know, by people who aren't society.
I mean, it's crazy.
It's like the people that...
I mean, I feel pretty betrayed. I mean, I'm from I'm kind of still in shock and
It's sad and yeah, yeah, especially with somebody you cared about and stuff
It's hurtful though, and I'm just glad I don't have that in real life. It's just on this internet
It's like you can't trust anybody and and I mean like somebody was threatening me already. Oh my god. Is that another right?
Here you are
They want to run one
One point, but at the season this is said stop using my legal name
Accusation there's a certain charge. Yeah, my name again or never talk about me
It said don't put my name with this charge with that person
They're gonna see my mother's name now
Like if I'm not always had your back
I know, Josie. Yes, you have. Yes, you have.
And baby girl, I've not always said you're back.
Yeah, and you're a sweetheart, ghost.
You're really awesome.
Yeah. And I'm sorry, I just sleep nights.
I was, you know, and, oh man, I woke up so early though tonight,
but you're cool and I like talking to you too, ghost.
You're cool.
Because you know what? I know, because I know this, I mean,
it's like, if I was really mean, you know, I have that information about that.
I see you.
You're mean.
Uh-huh. I was really mean and it's like
Come on don't come on don't tear up my blinds come on
Play the song for my baby girl
I'll tell you what her panties will fall after this song
We can't
I'm inside. Come on. I'm inside. Come on. Oh, yeah. They're
going to say, oh, she doesn't have a cat. They're like, they're
like, they're like, they're just they are. Yeah. They're
everybody here. They've seen them. Yeah. And I have insurance
often and murdered. Oh, no. I got I got all my teeth. Are you
kidding me? Come here boy cat. He's this one. He's he's so bad
though. Listen, I like my women just a little bit older. Yeah.
I like order women. I got I got four cats now. Oh, wow, but the baby I'll show you a picture
She's real thin and they told the office asked me to take her in because I said
She keeps running back when people try to take her permission. I got her
Oh, no, they let me keep them and you know adopt them and they appreciate me
I the ghost video here we go watch this one
I have a video of my friend the other feral cats that the neighbor has and I'll send it to you
They need to be adopted though cuz they've got
Here you go this is from my baby girl, okay, I need a name for boy cat
This is for my
Drink that. Drink that ash, girl.
You gotta get fat. Why are you so skinny?
That's a lot.
May I have permission?
Oh, and I have a pinkie name.
He rolls it loud like thunder on caffeine
Drop the steps like jokes
Keepin' the scene clean
I like this song. Thank you.
Alright, here we go.
Let's fuckin' go
And now we're flyin'
He's chaos with the halo
Wild but true
Help me down in the sky
Lost it's you
They can't see the light
He threw in my storm
May I permission?
How was your boy?
Oh, okay, and I got two black cats.
Coastal Reddy did he took the whole crowd.
Oh, Tanner.
Heart of gold voice of fire.
When gold shows up, the stakes get high.
What's she talking about?
No.
That's his whole crowd sound every.
Hater gets fun right round when the chat goes cold.
He brings it loud.
It's closed over, baby.
Sike is proud proud that's little
And no, I'm gonna like this party.
Let's fucking go!
It is! Thank you, y'all love it!
There you go. Okay. So, I, you know, I think the only responsible thing to say, you know what? That's weird. We finna have another guest over there.
Come on out.
That's weird. You have two black cats. One smaller than the other because I have two of them. The bully cat's got big. She was a baby on streets too and I've had her now for a while.
And the other one is smaller.
One time I had my look one of my cats came back his name was tux and he but he just came back for like a couple of weeks and then now he's
Not coming back and it's I don't want them out. Yeah, I just I don't want that happening because kitty one time got out and she was already
You know she's old and then remember and stuff and I lost over a couple days about her back and she was so lost like she's not recognizing people and then she passed away she was 20 almost 21
And the vet said he had to put her down. She was, you know, she was with herself and she she'd be confused and not seen too good
And you know, she was 20. I thought she'd live at least I don't how long do they live 25 or 30? Maybe
And she was slowing down so and I've had her for so long she was my first cat that I rescued from outside
And I have pictures all over on my IG.
You could see them below my pets.
I have them on Facebook.
And I even posted Boycat's picture
when he finally got on the tree yesterday.
I have a picture on my community post.
I'll put the other one where he finally falls asleep
comfortably.
Well, you know when I saw tonight like you sent me a link or had seen the link
It was like, you know, elbow had posted like you something about you know, what was it called? It was like it was a live
Yeah, I crashed though too, man. It's it's I recorded it, but I cracked on I mean, it's already been taken down
I have it. I have it. You know what's weird? I I fell asleep. I was exhausted
And I crashed and and then I woke up really really late and I saw my phone was still on recording and I remember it's like
Oh, wait a minute
He went live and I started recording it and I checked it because it said that it was removed for violation
Yeah, and when I checked my phone, I have it all so it didn't stop recording when I crashed
Yeah, because you get that on the on the computer. It'll sometimes stop. Well, but I mean, yeah
I mean I was a mod like because I he modded me like when I went to his he's he hasn't done a live since I think last year and I went in there
I was having fun as a mod and then all of a sudden I was unmodded very unceremoniously with that explanation
I think it was maybe Arthur was sort of complaining that I had a wrench and something like that so Arthur you're bad, but uh
Arthur is very too big
You yes, you can have one ghost, but next time I see you in the chat. Okay, well, you know what I call him for that show
Yes
Yeah, you know what I saw him do a long time ago, and that's why I didn't like him
But he seemed cool when he joined your panel. Yeah, but one time he was on on with Sam and
Talking shit about KK that she had a new channel and doing that
Yeah, that he's no good, yeah, I know that but still he was bashing KK and then I like KK and I watch her and
I was watching her live and there he came on her panel talking shit about same in three days later
Yeah
And summer join but did you by the way, it's like you hear what happened on patron they kicked me
They kicked you up aware
Say hi teacher. Yeah, who don't tell him paid to kick you off or something or they kicked you off
They pay to give me up a couple of times. Yeah, I mean that's the last one was 24 hours
It's like I don't believe that no one's given that do money. I don't think a lot of I seem to I don't believe it at all
Well, we don't know hey, what's up easy? Hey, look have you seen this picture of me? This is a picture of me
And I think I was an eighth grade
Are you serious? No, that's what we had we had a cross-dressing day or is it was are you there at school?
They did a cross
Since you want to talk to everyone about where you're from when do you become from Japan?
No, my dad would work for mobile oil. So we were
I was I was I was I was from Japan. No, I was born in New York. We just travel around the world
And see what's again, you're Japanese, but go stay with me. I don't remember Japan
I was like two and a half years old. I was two and a half years old
Yeah, I was I was a toddler and then we moved back to South America
No, my dad worked for mobile oil. He'd had a great job with them, you know, so
Yeah, we so we so we lived around the world because of his job they make great money and he made a lot of money
and my mom
Military because you made him stand to attention. He said no because the places we went to
There like we lived in Lagos, Nigeria, too, there's no American military there
You're a prince
No, I'm just kidding I and I because they have these Nigerians called yahoo boys and they say oh
They do that that a cat fishing kind of scam where they like send
psyche instead of you because I'd rather take psyche you just yeah
Hey, I'm answering him. Okay. Go ahead. Ghost. I was answering him. He asked me about Japan
It was a toddler. It was a little bit. You're bad. You're being bad ghost bad ghost
sorry yeah um but um but then i don't know if you do pages um i and x page
what about page you know who she is i i don't think so i don't
She's very nice. She's a Canadian. She's part, you know, part Indian. I've never been to Canada
Never been to Canada. I've never been to Hawaii
Golf of Hawaii's awesome. No, I never I played I was a semi pro racket player a bracket ball player when I was in college
And I played basketball
Yeah guard
Well page is somebody else on my show. She's she has a she has her own show and she also does she does tear our
Bridgings and stuff and she's written. She's very sweet. Can I get a card reading, please?
Yes, you can in a few minutes, but just let me say one thing. I'm fucking back
Alice did a live
tonight after during after my show took to the rebut whatever I was I was showing and
Hold on a second and
At the end of it. She goes after Paige like you know who's just like she doesn't even know it's just
It's a different lady
Prairie page
Blonde she's like I like summer. Yeah summer is cool, but I like you
I like you too ghost. Yeah, you're cool and you're funny
You're so little man you get a game wait, baby
Oh, let me see, where are you?
Oh baby, I'm trying to get some food for you.
No, my, my, the kid, the kid that I, I took him.
No, I was talking about the cat, my bad, my bad, my bad.
Oh.
This is called for the forest enchantment deck.
I have an animal, but they have animals on them, okay?
There's a forest enchantment.
I'll do one for both of you.
Okay.
If you don't give me a leo card, we've been fighting.
Well, Leo's the son, and so we have to, there's a son.
We're gonna fight if you're not gonna give me a Leo.
Okay, these are nice cards. I got these cards on Timu, and so it's like...
I'm a Leo.
And so, they make these mini decks of every deck, okay?
I'm gonna fight you.
So this is for Ghost, and then I'll get one for Inaq.
No, I'm just gonna get one, yeah.
Okay, Ghost, what do you got?
Okay, oh my gosh, where are my glasses? I got my glass. I need my my my big
Okay
The liar goes is the liar. Oh
I'm catching up. I don't know who so I don't know somebody's been dishonest with you or
You know
Yeah, it looks like you though in the picture. Yeah, you gosh, it doesn't look like me looks like you
It's like it looks like you're a must-do-you-go.
I'm not a liar. Oh, come on.
I'm just kidding. Hold on.
I told you I would.
You said Nigeria, but Flip Flat is giving some good alchemy lessons.
I ain't nobody said Nigeria.
I never once said Nigeria.
Oh, Victoria Island. We lived on Victoria Island. I was 14 and 14 there.
No, in Regal's Nigeria, Victoria Island.
Okay, he's giving the alchemical the stages, and it says black, which is negrado.
That's putrification, white is element, means purification, yellow means citrinitas, which
It means ultimate completion. So you see red and yellow and black and white
Next you got goes you got the weaver of challenges and so you have somebody like maybe
You know, there's somebody that's you know organizing some things that maybe a challenge is but there's a reward for this
I think there's and this is like
Well, I mean it's like let me see I mean these are like I don't think these are necessarily like the traditional cards
But let me give me a fucking Leo card. I'm gonna crush you. Okay
This is a tool boom. I'm gonna fucking this bitch tonight. Oh
Come on, don't you don't use the word?
Goes you got a sun card you got a sun card
Cuz look this is called the five of visions and look there's like this ball which is like the Sun and there's the frog
I like it. Okay. Can she kiss me so I can't be a frog anymore kiss you. I mean, but you have to find the ball for you
Look at all the rabbits goes
No, I have a story about
Fucking rabbit he says the rabbits
There's a woman in England that um you call me a hair
There's a woman
To and surrey surrey outside of london surrey england. Um, I have family there my mom my mom's sister
Married an english man. Yeah, that's beautiful. Go ahead. I've been
Well, there's a woman in england that she started giving birth to parts of rabbits and stuff
And all the and she went to the
putting dead rabbits up herself, and then like...
What? Yeah, put them in the... Yeah, drown them.
It's a terrible story. But, um, yeah, they were
defining these dead rabbits around... Oh, look at this one. Hold on.
Oh, excuse me.
They had this big fish.
Just by that.
They had this big fish swimming around right there, okay?
That's I'm a fisherman. So it's okay. I read for you. I next I'll put you some part. Yeah. Yeah, you yeah
Look at this you have the four of boons and so look at this
Like sold a pie
and you see you're at your side, you know,
pumping and the guy's walking away.
Okay, so that one.
It tastes like blue hair.
Something kind of trade is successful.
Oh, you got the suspension, which is like the hangman,
but it's also like, you know, you're taking a,
it's like a breath, you get a break from it.
You're taking a time when you shouldn't.
You're gonna see something for a different perspective
because it looks like down.
Almost like a womb, like a womb energy, like a-
Hey, yo!
What do you mean upside down?
Hey, you know, fucking no good person that's suspended, but it's like they're almost in the womb.
They're like a moment like it's suspended in the womb.
Just seeing things from a different perspective.
You also have this one.
So we're a fucker.
You got the wise woman.
I annexed the wise woman.
That's why I have to fuck it.
So why are you high?
You're high intuition.
You also have wisdom and it's like also a different kind of wisdom than maybe.
is common you know you've been uncommon with them and you can also like I'm gonna fuck
her oh my gosh here's a picture of ghosts you got the five of challenges
no bitch already got my cards don't give me no no no you're literally on the card she she's
got the ghost card yeah i'm definitely gonna fuck her ghost card
I'm definitely gonna fuck her this little challenge troll you got a you're gonna get got a beat down with a stick
Oh, I'm definitely fucking there. She got to go
This is like the wheel of fortune. Oh, yeah, things are really going in your favor also
We're gonna put together for you also
Psyche, right? Yeah, you already got that goes card. I'm finna fuck you. You're a no good
Oh my bad, okay
But you have to watch out because there's there might be like, you know,
there might be a tower, like I think in a tower moment,
the towers will always like, you know, clear space for stuff, for what's right.
But something else has to be cleared out first.
And it could be, you know, surprising, but look at this.
You got this 10 of visions. This is great. This is like these unicorns.
I'm not going to be the unicorns are beautiful.
I love unicorns unicorn is a pot. Is it probable?
No, it's possible. Maybe but it's not probable. Am I fucking tonight? Is it possible? No. I mean, yeah, it's possible
No, I'm not gonna fuck her up. I'm finna give her some babies
No
That's over here knocking something down over here. I like I love this for you. I and I don't want this is it says the wise
Hold on. Uh, it says oh come here. No, there's my dark glasses. Where are my other glasses?
Yes, ma'am. Where do I go?
Damn you'd not give everything over. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am. Yes ma'am.
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
Well, I don't know
Yeah, you gotta be careful, you know, there's yeah, just be careful
Okay, so the stairway
Oh my god, oh
This is a stairway to heaven. He comes ladder Kundalini rising is this
You need water water also, I heard something called the um, there's something called the library of Babel
And it's like, I don't know if it's real or not.
It has every single book ever written or will be written,
every single word that's ever been said, what we said.
And it's like, yeah, all these libraries
and it goes up forever.
I don't like you taking my bitches real quick.
I don't like you talking about my girls.
Every time I bring a girl up here, you try to take her.
Are you gay or not?
You try to take my females from me.
Gross.
Yeah, stop trying to take my females, bro.
Oh, he's doing a reading.
Oh, my bad, my bad, my bad.
My bad, my bad, my bad, my bad.
You know, but it's interesting.
There's something on the library of Babbel,
and it's like, I don't know if it's a theoretical thing,
but it says, but then like every book will have like,
I'll be like pages of like patterns and stuff like that.
And it's like everything I've ever written,
goes on forever and kind of like...
Okay, I don't know.
You never mind.
Oh, there's Rudy.
There's Rudy.
I fucking burped.
Oh, you want me to say something about that?
Oh, Biruti is cute.
Oh, did you hear the boy cat?
He just loud me out.
He's so vocal, though.
Boy cat. Oh, he's I call him boy cat. I need a name for him. Okay. Well, I was thinking like
His picture is on my community post when he finally got on the cat tree yesterday and he was sleeping
I'll have another cuter picture the baby that I took in that they asked
Beautiful I'll see what he looks like I'm gonna go see it
He's big man, but he destroys the the
the blinds over there by the living room downstairs. It's like he'll look out the window and he just
I want to get the man's man to fix it. Yeah about the the the boy cat. Yeah, I love animals.
Here we go. Well, I'll show you a picture of her boy cat. Let me see. I know it's in the community.
Is this him? Oh my god. Okay. Yeah, boy cat. That's boy cat. Okay. I'll post I'll post the new
take her in, because she's been struggling out there by herself, and yeah.
And how many lives do you think, can I eat that pussy nine times?
Oh my god, I'll tell you that. Yeah, that's good.
Oh, come on. Here, look, there's a boy cat.
Yeah, that's a boy cat. That's the one that's vocal,
the one that tries to mess with my blinds downstairs,
and they had to come in and fix it, and now he's trying to go at it again.
I don't know what, he's got an obsession with tearing it down, I guess.
I see, let me see, I see, he's beautiful, let me see.
Yeah, he is beautiful, he's sweet,
but he's the one that's here in the background
that's all we have in the whole thing.
Do you have a favorite letter or a favorite,
like kind of like, do you have like a?
I think she's my favorite, she's my favorite letter.
She's like a Scarlet Leather, she sounds so beautiful.
She sent me a picture and she sounds beautiful.
Yeah, I get Bobby or like,
It's a boy home. Let me see. Yeah, I can't think of it. I'll just name and you know nick name
We don't care
They're beautiful in every life. Yeah, thank you. I think of what's the guy from?
Let me see. I guess it would be richie richie
Richie you think you know what that might be a cute name
I just couldn't think of a name for him because I wasn't playing on keeping them, but I guess he's here. He just
I know, because yeah, because once you give the name, it's like pretty much the deal, the
deal.
Yeah.
No, I don't know if you really do that if you like biblical names or something like that
Yeah, any good name for me
Gabriel, angel names the Gabriel or something like Tyler
Go cute after ghosts. Yeah, you know what? Yeah, Tyler. Maybe a Tyler. Do you think that's a cool name for him?
Hi, I would go with Gabriel or Michael, but Tyler's literally third option
I agree. I think so. That's better. Michael is too basic. But how about the girl? How about you just instead of something like Michael? How about you just call me mine?
Oh, no
Well ghosts you are a charmer you just take your outdoor cat buddhishes. They're all empty neighborhood cats are good to go
Neighbor cats. Rudy's a happy cat. He has come a long way. Yeah. I got Rudy last year. He
And listen every time we disagree we can call psyche
Yeah, right
Yeah, I've never disagreed with you baby girl and that's in the real life. Yeah
Thank you
Yes, oh, yeah, I know that flip-flop. So Tyler because I remember watching this thing about Tyler Perry
Right, but Tyler Perry like this woman thought that okay, he had stolen her eggs and had her child and stuff
Yeah, Tyler guards the door of the Masonic Lodge. Yes, and okay. That's a good name
We're not a bitch with seven foot tall. Hey Tyler. So it's so ghost you to guard. Are you a Mason ghost?
My dad was my dad and his dad were yeah
Well, you know, I have a my part of my genealogy is Mero Vengeans who are
The French were they're called the long-haired Kings. There's a French
royalty monarchy and like, you know, hmm hundreds of years ago. They actually and the and their ancestor was actually a
It's called the Kinotar and it was a
Half a minute tar have fish
Hey, no, that's what you're called. Oh psyche like my dad's last name
He was trying to they were they they burnt him at the stake because he was trying to take over the kingship of England
And he was something to do with the king of scots or something
Yeah, I'll show you the name and yeah, because
my brother went to the what was it to Utah he went to the church the
Mormon church where they have the history and
the people they they go there from all over the world just to see their backgrounds or the
history and everything and it's there about our
are relative and I didn't understand it, I was a kid, but yeah, I read about him. So he was like, something that was done.
Was it a nice Templar person?
I don't know, you'll see it. He was burnt at the stake because they were trying to take over England and I don't know, he was a crusader.
Well, I have actually, in the United States, everyone knows what the...
Salem witch trials, but there was actually Connecticut. It wasn't a witch thing
It was that they went from Scotland to go try to take over the kingdom
Whatever and he was I don't know what I forget what he was, but I didn't follow that I just you know
But yeah, he's in there and yeah, he was somebody
Get the rocks stone them and burn them
Hey, yeah
And there's been terrible barbaric things I just can't believe when you hear some of the horrible things that they would do to people like
You know, it's like all the brazen bull where they would
You
Actually, I mean, it's like, you know, Catholicism is paganism basically ghost. I mean, it's like, so
You dog
I'm not gonna fucking keep repeating myself do it now
Yeah, you're not gonna suck down be a good boy. Yeah, that's me. It is interesting because bathroom it is like
I can ask you're a fucking pig. Yeah, it's like pan, but then it's like there's a lot of other things
Anything you fucking believe and you made it up
Stop it. Well, you can say the same thing about any religion ghost. I mean really it's like it's all ideas at the end of the day
Everything in one
Go see first of all
That's what psyche the boy cat is is on the cat tree again
This is the second time to well the second day
But she didn't want anything to do with it because he was from outside, too
Yeah, he's really comfortable and the bully cat is on the bottom of the tree. So she's not kissing at him or growling
See Arthur were you in see you weren't were you in stand man's or were you in Eldos tonight complaining that you know some
Arthur we thought you saying I was a predator protector in Eldos chat tonight, and I should never wrench
He's in there you mean he's saying that right now in your town
Where's his wrench? I'm just asking was that him in Eldos tonight that said
Psyche has a predator on it. Yeah, he was like, okay, so it was a different archer. Okay, I'll give you a wrench back
Yeah, he was live. He went live doing a whole thing about beta. He didn't leave a wrench
I have the whole video. I told you it recorded everything. I fell asleep
I woke up and I thought maybe it ended or something
But now I have the whole thing where it said thank you in the end over two hours long
I have the whole video Psyche. Yeah
Yeah, at least I mean the guy's talking about Ellie fuzz leave. I there's a great book called the dog the dogma
I don't know. That's not good. I was like, yeah, I posted the video, but I'll and I'll unlist it for you to see
It's there. Okay. Well, I next have it live, but I have the whole thing. Okay. You're gonna post it
It's posted, but I have it on private because they it looks like they took that for
Was it you took it down or they was reported, but I have it there. You can see it unlisted
Okay, if you unlist it maybe like you maybe Arthur can contact you and you can give me. Yeah, okay. Yeah, that's that way I can
Only he would be able to see it if I give him the dress link. Yeah
because it was about, you know, I guess tonight on Vitas,
like someone can put a picture of Eldo,
is there a profile picture?
So he came back and put a picture of somebody,
I think Kate, and then she put the two and let him on.
And he's like, well, you're letting this person use my
picture, then why can't I use this picture?
And then she started arguing and turned into a big,
yeah, you put it on Rumble.
You're gonna have to-
I didn't watch it.
Yeah, I didn't watch it.
I just saw that I have the whole thing
and it was over two hours, two hours and 20 minutes.
Yeah.
I haven't marked it all I did was I was surprised it's still on there because I crashed
And then showed it was over two hours and I thought well, wait a minute
It's recorded when I was crashed and it sure did and I forwarded it
And it shows the whole thing until the end where it says thank you
So it's posted it's posted, but it's it's good
Play that play I can I'll play I'll turn to play later, but but why was it taken down play this hole?
I guess they reported it or something, but they must have reported it afterwards because I have the whole video
Let's see. Well, Arthur posted this link that says 60 year old woman being racist. Okay, let me check it out
Okay, you want to see I'll check it out. I'll give it a chance. Okay. Yeah, he wants to see what you didn't have to know
You think of the video
Ghost left. Okay, so here is the ghost left. Yeah, here's this one. Okay. You um, I'll pull it up here
This art from Arthur to six-year-old lady being racist
Okay. Oh, thank you. He's a sweet message. He just said yeah, I like ghost. He's cool. That's forever
Lord
Hey, it's on the bottom bitch
salmon's new super stories. What are you going to say? What are you going to do? Hold on. Are you going to keep
there? I've only heard salmon say that. Don't worry about salmon. You don't have to bring salmon.
Your nigger ass doesn't have to bring salmon. Your nigger ass.
I think it's going to go. Salmon will always fucking be salmon. And I have fucking rock with salmon.
So what the fuck are you going to say about salmon? You fucking bitch. Put your nigger ass in the middle.
Scunch it up and fucking throw it in your mom's face. Oh
Look at your penis and we're in wonder why you don't you haven't you don't have a nigger talk. Oh my god
Oh my goodness. When was this or no, we're doing the nigga challenge tonight nigga
Where did you get this? Is this today? Is that a live or...
Is that her?
Get the fuck out of here.
Jesus Christ, man. Look at this.
Well, I mean, you don't have to be Jesus Christ into this.
This is disgusting.
Jesus is disgusting.
Your mom is a nigger.
Your mom is a nigger and she's disgusting.
Damn, seriously, this is the end word all the time.
Appreciate it.
Well, yeah. Michigan niggers forever.
Six months ago.
Oh, my lord.
Are you still in the bottom, bitch?
I mean, how much further?
What are you going to do?
Hold on.
Are you going to kiss her?
I'm going to get up.
I'm going to kiss her.
Don't worry about that.
That was it.
Okay. That was it.
Oh my God.
Bita.
And Bita.
She gets vile and that's the way she gets.
It's like, yeah, it's just, I don't know.
It's shocking.
I mean, it's like, but yeah.
I mean, yeah.
So, but all of a sudden during that,
during that, uh, the live, I see big clips and big clips goes,
Alexander's asking for your beta and so Alexander had a live-in and said at beta at Christine at
Crystal Anne
On the front of it and then Crystal Anne keeps it. She allowed her on her panel going off with Jamie and Nancy
They're the ones that cut her off and they can show proof and I keep telling them y'all keep saying you're gonna take the link with with
Tate but they don't they don't take the link. It's like take the link already, you know, I take take the link
Well, it's not like they have to show themselves and just take the link.
Don't say, oh, if she drops the link, and when they do, you don't take it.
It was crazy.
They're all like going against it.
They're like, oh, you know, these terrible men, and they're like, we need to grow power.
Let's all get together and like, you know, love each other as girls, because we tear
each other down, which is not a bad message, but it just sounded very strange coming from
this group.
Alex and Crystal back together and then Alex was like continuing to say,
oh, Bita is such a wonderful person.
She likes Sam and for her, I mean, it's like everything has just gone top.
Yeah, that's what's sad.
I can't deal with that people just back and forth like that, you know,
and they could be really cool.
Um, because I like her, you know, we should all be just cool with the first in the first place and not like fighting
And I mean people have differences, but it's like and I agree like we can have differences opinion
Not we can be we can disagree without being disagreeable, right? Yeah
Yeah, I mean it's like it just seemed very strange and then you know, she went after Paige of course, which was this
Page has not even met her. I don't think and then she's calling page of trans
Which is just
Alexandra, oh, yeah, I don't know whose pages but yeah, you guys were friends though
And you know what I've found is that she is sensitive like we are so let's not talk about her because you guys
I just want to say this though because yeah, yeah, because
She's gone way too far, and she's still,
and then she's alive, it has my mom's name.
She doesn't say my name, she says my mom's name.
I'm the son of, she has my mom's name.
And that is not her, not hers to do.
I mean, I know her, I know her parents' names
and stuff like that, I know her, I know everything.
Okay, and it's like, I don't do that
because I wouldn't do that
because I'm not like a fucking dick.
And Paige didn't do anything to Alex ever.
She didn't even remember a matter, I don't think.
But,
I mean, it's just so sad.
Okay, but I'll leave it, because I know it's-
Yeah, leave it.
Yeah, I mean, if you're going to talk about it,
maybe one day you haven't talked with her about it.
I know she won't talk to me.
That's the problem.
She didn't even talk to me as soon as she separated,
she wouldn't talk to me anymore.
I was banned from her chat immediately.
I'm banned from everything.
And that's it.
I mean, it's like, and so it's frustrating.
I didn't get a chance to defend myself or even find out.
I said, what did I do?
She goes, you know what you did.
I didn't do anything really and then it had a file to be called a extorter blackmailer an elder abuser a loser
I mean, I'm blub. She said I'm blackmailing my parents. I mean, there's just so many fucking bad things
But go stop. I think she is very sensitive and like she said, you know that I'm sensitive and like her and look I've
Said stuff like that. I'd blow I mean I go nuts too when somebody hurts my feelings
But it's like that's if somebody does I didn't do anything
That's the that's the point is that I didn't do I didn't I did nothing for her to do this
And then it's like I can't even respond and then it's like and then to docks not even judges me
But you know my loved ones and stuff like that and then have everyone like be like, oh, you know, they don't they don't really care
And it's like wow, it's like
And I really hated that much because it's like it just feels like something wrong, but just give her time
You know, it'll take time and and just talk to her about it
I'll talk about about it. I'm live though because there's other people that want to instigate. So
She's doing lives about me
I just want to show you one thing because this is what I this is what you got met is like a math because she said
She got mad because she said oh, I'd misrepresented this tweet like it was like recent
I don't know when this tweet was made it probably made between 2020 and 2023 or something like that, but um, I don't know about that
I'll just say this tweet real quick
On the top of it, it says,
tonight I will specifically state to every individual
who has ever targeted me or my family,
I will end your existence.
Okay, that sounds like somebody that doesn't
like people messing with me.
Of course, yeah, that's your family.
And then at the bottom, for a few years,
my adversaries have assumed that I'd never be part of their,
of the manifestation of their absolute worst fears
in regards to their quote unquote loved ones
and themselves, most importantly,
because that's who will be blamed
being held accountable by the worst of the worst.
or to the worst of the worst.
So that's what I was showing that she said that she's,
I don't know what she's trying to say.
It doesn't matter if she said it yesterday
or 10 years ago, I think that's her sentiment,
especially with what she's doing now.
So that's what I wanted to say.
I'm not trying to say she said that today.
I don't even know, I'm not gonna Twitter anymore,
it's called X, but okay.
So, but anyway, that's pretty fucked up though,
to be one who want to be like the manifestation
of somebody's worst fears towards their most loved ones.
They'll be blamed not her right. That's the thing. Mm-hmm. Hmm. Just seems a little strange. There's a link coast
Okay, but anyway, let's look we can change the topic. How most Hollywood movies portray them
Momomo structures as what?
Momotos structure and its life's journey monomyth. Okay the monomyth. Yeah, I like the fool's journey
Which is like who wrote the fool's journey. Mm-hmm
Pretty the name right now, but have you ever seen him? Have you heard of birds of paradise Ion X?
I've heard of it, but what does it mean?
I've heard of it, so I'm not familiar.
Well, birds of paradise are actually like in South America,
right, aren't you?
My mom, yes, we have South American.
Well, a lot because her dad's family was from Spain.
Her mom was German.
She would say they escaped the Holocaust
when her mom was pregnant with her.
And then they went to South America and then she was born.
And her mom passed away giving birth, and then her dad took his life, so, yeah, she was raised and adopted by family.
Yep, so this is like called the spectacle of these, so this is the birds of paradise, they're actually birds.
Yeah, I was seeing.
They made, they made, this is their mating dance, oh, sorry, this is their mating dance.
I'm gonna show the screen, okay, so check this out, you're gonna love this.
I remember if you're saying yeah, I remember if he and then they're known like in South America
I was there as a little kid till I was eight and then moved around again. There's other places. These are amazing
I think you'll be surprised
The character of the forest changes as you descend becoming ever darker and damper
favoring different kinds of animals and plants
That's South America
Less than two percent of the sunlight reaches the floor, but even here there is extraordinary variety
In the great island of New Guinea
There are forty two different species of birds of paradise each more bizarre than the last. Oh my gosh
I'm like, yeah, this is beautiful
This forest is so rich that nourishing food can be gathered very quickly
That leaves the male six-plumed bird a paradise with time to concentrate on other matters like tidying up his display area
Yeah, look at this thing so crazy
Display everything must be
There's Martha these birds
The same if it has before the girl gets there
Elite is ready. Oh my god. Oh, wow
Yeah
Before very impressive but no one is watching
The superb bird of paradise calls to attract a female and he has more luck
But what does he have to do to really impress her?
That's a female they look different huh, or no, that's a friend of the oh wow
The male is the one with the blue. Look at that, look at that.
Damn, and it's the same green to birds. I mean, that's, it looks like a different type of bird, but look at that, damn.
I've never seen that.
She retires to consider her verdict.
Right? It's a little, it's a little.
It's hard not to feel deflated when even your best isn't good enough.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's awesome, I never yeah and I did want to show you something too,
Thursday when I was a kid they showed me this thing in school and it was like really touching
and I mean it's a really kind of a little bit sad story. It's they had a there's a gorilla
named Coco and let me see if I can find something. Let me see yeah here's so this is Coco and the
Check this out here. I hope this is the original story. I don't know if you've heard Coco guys, but check this story out
Okay, here we go
Hey, here we go. So it stands out in people's memories is because there's an emotional surprise there
There's a giant. Oh, yeah, I've seen that. That's is that cocoa. Yeah, yeah, he passed away. Yeah
Oh, they showed Michael Jackson's Chimpanzee, what was his name, Bubbles, and a relative
went to see him and he was showing Coco, I mean, he was showing him Michael's picture
and you know what, he had this human-like expression, like he was kind of sad and so
happy to see it and smiled.
Cheerio, and then he he moved his head sideways like to tell him. Yeah, I remember I clipped it. It's beautiful
So they remember people
Yeah
So sweet. He's a baby. He's big now, too, and he's old. But yeah, it's a recent video
Wow
Only live 13 years
Cocoa passed away or no Cocoa was alive for a while
So the monkey I mean the cat didn't live that long one of them it said that they did it look like
He named the first one ball and it got hit by a car. Oh
My god, how sweet
I remember Coco that he didn't he do sign language. Yeah, yeah, remember him
I have a-
Dar.
Oh.
A lady who's-
Dar.
My, well, one of my cats, her name is Dara.
I call her the bully.
She's a bully now.
So her nickname is-
Littles, because she was little when I got her,
but she's big now and she's a bully.
Don't go away.
Oh my God.
Don't go.
Hey, are you are you able to send that like that video that he wants to see?
How do I get it so he sees it because it's on private now and if I put it on listed
Don't go.
If you get that on listed and then you put give me put the link in the back chat with wallies in the back
So it's hard as it'll it'll kick me off though right now because I'm on my phone
I'll do that and I'll text it to you when I get off here. I'll text it to you before Arthur leaves
okay perfect um yeah because i want to see the video oh yeah i want to see koko if you have
another one but arthur can you hang on until he finishes with a koko video i love koko
he meets mr rogers and then let's see what else i mean i want to see when he met um i guess this
is like uh i see he met mr rogers which is pretty cool but uh let's see so here's um i want to see
Okay, I remember there was one in national geography. Yeah, I'll clear something up though. Um, you know, I
Your crystal keeps saying my name and and our two other friends names and they were done with her for a long time ago
And so she keeps saying their name because one of them blocked her for good because she wouldn't she wouldn't block that person
And always would cry to her about stuff and she'd be on the phone till she went to sleep
But this person is done with her
And she keeps calling them out even on alex's live and it's because they're done and the only reason i was in her chat because she was saying our names again and i don't watch her you know somebody let me know she was on there saying my name.
And she acts like i'm trying to be friends with her no i'm the one that was done and i show the proof of me telling her that when she was blowing me up i'm not going at anybody.
Um, but I just went up there because I also needed to know, uh, you know, I'm, I'm an advocate for rescues and stuff here in the city and.
I needed to see that video to the truth about Brandon. They said that he attacked a dog
But that doesn't open for me because I saw the regular video that there was shared
I didn't see him attack a dog. He was chased a dog
Lady was yelling at him. And so he went and banged on her door. That's all I saw so he's and I asked crystal
sent rescind the half gamble rescind it to me and she wouldn't so that means that
the video that everybody saw is the truth because where's this video about Brandon hitting a dog?
I don't know. You know, she would have sent it or played it if it was true. So I caught her in
that. That's the only reason I went up there because, you know, I mean, you're not going to
talk about our, you know, my friends who've been cool with me and I've never had an issue,
maybe one time with one of them,
But um, yeah, she just needs to stop nobody's trying to be friends with her
I've been done because I don't need this shit
I feel that she just used me when she was contacting me in the hospital to come defend her
I don't know that's all I had to say cap brought in a mouse. Oh my god, Lola. Oh, my gosh
Straight around here. Oh, is this one cocoa to the
Yeah, this one's cocoa to here we go. Oh, yeah, cocoa is beautiful in the misty hills
just south of San Francisco, I'm about to come face to face with the most famous gorilla in
the world, Coco. Meet my friend Coco, the gorilla who talks. And if you don't believe me, watch
and see for yourself. But they kept him in a cage his whole life. Look, he looks sad. Yeah.
It's amazing being this close, staring into the eyes of a 200 kilogram gorilla.
But it's even more remarkable to have a conversation with her.
What do you want for dinner, Coco?
What do you want to eat?
Nuts.
Uh-oh.
Nuts would be nice.
I'll remember to bring nuts.
To be honest, at first, I'm skeptical.
But psychologist Professor Penny Penison claims she's taught Cocoa...
She put her finger in her eye and put it down because I think she's, um, I don't know,
it's her whole language, I guess.
...Cocoa can understand.
I thought she was meant to be sad.
...to have spoken English.
Your baby?
Oh, yeah, when I ask Coco where her toy doll is she does seem to understand and goes off to look for it
Oh, so she has a big room. Okay. I thought she was kept in a cage
Yeah, she's bringing it over though. This is this is one of the favorites, but she was all alone. You know
I doubt there is a child in the world who hasn't dreamed of being like Dr. Dolittle and talking to the animals.
That's probably true. That would have been me.
Was that your dream when you were younger?
I was totally, my world was animals. I was fascinated with them.
He would have lived longer if she was free.
43 years ago, this incredible relationship began when 24-year-old Penny first saw baby
Coco at an American zoo.
Penny wanted to unlock the world of communication between gorillas and humans.
She convinced the zoo owners that she should take over caring for Coco.
It's a beautiful relationship you have with her.
So it's, it is mother and daughter and it's not all smooth rides, especially when adolescent
hits.
Do you have arguments?
Sometimes.
And it's like who's going to win this one.
She says open time there.
It's lovely to meet you.
We need everybody in here.
She tells Penny she wants me to come into her cage.
Oh honey, I know what you're planning, you're planning to have this really great visit.
She wants a party, doesn't she?
And she wants to open the door.
But unfortunately, getting any closer than I am now is restricted for everyone's well-being.
Sorry, I can't do that today.
Professor Patterson's four decades of research with Coco is now the longest-running eight-language
study in history.
But she had more human contact then.
Look, she's happier as a baby.
And look how miserable it is that they won't even go into caves.
Yeah
Results speak for themselves
But mainstream behavioral scientists strongly dispute claims that an ape like Coco can actually talk with sign language
They say Penny's merely projecting her own meanings onto Coco's gestures.
Love, love, love, love, love, do, do, do, do, you.
I know you want them all in here.
Yeah, you do.
Yeah, the young scientists do believe, rigidly deny, that you are communicating with an ape, like Coco.
Well, I think in some sense it doesn't fit into the worldview.
Kind of like when the world was thought to be flat, and it turned out to be around.
That upset a lot of people.
Incredibly, not only does Penny believe Coco understands words,
but she's now also at a point where she's developing her own vocabulary.
Coco coined her own term for Penny's jewellery.
She's come up with that herself.
She comes up with them on her own.
And we didn't really have a word for ring,
but she called it a finger bracelet.
Which makes sense.
What a great name.
So, and a mask was an eye hat and so on.
And were you shocked when she started doing that?
Did she go beyond what you as a scientist thought was possible?
Well, I was very...
intrigued by that, because that was another evidence,
more evidence that there's a talent in there
that's intensely creative.
We're not on this equipment.
Even as we video her, Coco takes an interest
in our fluffy camera microphone,
and she's clearly asking Penny what it is.
And why am I on a page do you have some kind of something I've missed that next time flower
That's not a flower
What is there anything the microphone for that fluffy stuff?
Not actually a flower, but I I didn't see the other thing you sign. It's a microphone
look how sad it's like she got big and no more human contact human interaction yeah you're right
but it's equally obvious this hasn't been a normal upbringing for a gorilla no it's not
when penny found cocoa a potential mate this younger gorilla called michael there was hope
Oh, no. Oh, no. But while the two became firm friends, they never made it
No
No, she just didn't have contact with other
Gorillas
And has been asking for a family. Yeah, we have been striving to create one for her, but it's not it's not easy
It screwed up her life. That's what they did.
Tragically, Michael died several years ago and that sent Coco into a deep depression.
See, that's not fair. She was all alone in a cage when she got bailed.
A visit by comedian Robin Williams in 2012 changed all that.
Yeah, he did go in to see her. He insisted.
She'd seen that he was a funny man and
She was grieving at that time. She had lost Michael and
She hadn't smiled. She wasn't eating very much. She wasn't talking very much
She was sleeping very much and he visited and for the first time
She smiled she initiated a game of tickle
Uh, he insisted on going in there.
Yeah, that was a very special relationship.
I think he's getting special treatment, right?
Mm-hmm.
Well, they didn't want him in there with him.
When Robin Williams died two years later in 2014,
Penny Patterson claims Coco grieved for him.
We need to talk about abstract concepts.
I mean, one of the greatest abstract concepts for humans,
of course, is the whole notion of life and death.
Cocoa she does what does Cocoa describe death to be well
She said that when you die you go into a comfortable hole and
We blow you kiss goodbye
You were very very beautiful
She liked that comment, and they won't join with her.
No, I don't, yeah.
I'm so excited to meet you, Coco.
She says, well, then do that.
Just open this gate, you know.
She says this is what she's been
aiming for the whole time.
P. Patterson's four decades of work with Coco tell an extraordinary story of a life-long commitment.
See, even had her at home and then they'd believe her in a cave.
While most scientists have given up on ape communication, they simply say it's not possible,
Penny remains fervent in her belief.
She says it's not just possible to talk with this magnificent gorilla.
She also thinks Coco still has a lot to tell us.
It's been lovely to meet you.
We share so much of their DNA, don't we?
About 98%.
What does Coco think of us humans?
It was like that, yeah, that was, I mean, so sweet.
Yeah, I remember that watching that I mean it's like the whole thing is like there's a big story was like they got
Coco kitten and Coco fell in love with the kitten and the kitten actually like passed away
I had my car and Coco got so sad and then they brought Coco was but it's so interesting. Yeah, I mean
But I can see like, you know, you're really so empathic
that you can tell the gorilla didn't like being locked up.
Yeah, she wanted them in there and look at that.
I remember that actor, Williams or whatever,
he insisted on being with her
because they said you're safety or whatever.
And he insisted and Coco fell in love with him
and look at them, they were keeping her in a cage
and she was wanting them to come in.
I mean, you could tell she's hurt
Oh, no, that hate humans sometimes especially ignorant humans. They should have never kept her like that. That's
Well, you know
Or because it's like what the royal sheep because sometimes when they're when they're raised by humans that
They can't go in the wild, right? And so it's and then it's very difficult to
To figure out, you know, so pretty much the old navy chimpanzee next
A little old navy chimpanzee. Yeah any request for old navy chimpanzee was
For the old Navy chimpanzee
Yeah, I do love a I love nature. I I love nature films and
you know, I mean it's like I think we're kind of
Detached from me be cash from nature. Oh my god, so the old Navy like it is the old Navy
Chimpanzee, what do you I don't I don't see anything like that
But oh my god, oh my god, then there's a sad story this guy had a fancy and then like they had they had they had to like, you know
Give it up
Yeah
When you got too big and then they visited him and then like
They had given a came a candy bar or something like that at this little like place
He was in a cage and another change so jealous it broke the broke the cage down and
Ripped off the guy's nose and something like that, but
Oh my god. Yeah, the chimpanzees can be mean those two because look at that lady that got her face
bitten off and
The the chimp knew her but yeah, it was dangerous
So purple would tweet everything and they she's never done anything
But if this it's like my case in life to sit him free. It's just stupid
Exactly, it would have had babies if she was out there free with the rest of the
You know the gorillas
Yeah, I'm sorry. I don't see anything. Oh, yeah. Okay. I found the old Navy commercial. Okay. Here we go. Yeah
This is a 1997. There was an old Navy commercial
See if this is good. Here we go. And we got good chat going on too. Don't look guys
Okay, I didn't I didn't see I didn't see a chimpanzee there the guys come on. Are you joking? I mean, please don't call
I was so rude
There was a chimpanzee in there. They were just showing that a little clip of a chimpanzee
Yeah, yeah, okay, you can learn okay. So if you know how to read the dollar bill correctly, you know about the dollar bill
No, I mean, what what about it? Okay, so on the back of the dollar bill if you if you look on one side
It says well, there's a pyramid, right?
Yes, and but it's not really but if the pyramid it has no top on it, right?
Do I have a dollar? I don't think I have a dollar pocket. I have a dollar. Good morning. Okay, but
There is but it's it but it's easy. It was but it's an Egyptian symbolism, right? And it's interesting
We have an American dollar bill. We have an Egyptian sim like a pyramid, right? And it has
the eye on the pyramid, which is the sun,
because that creates the capstone.
The other side, there's a bird holding some arrows
and things like that.
That bird is like the phoenix.
People will say it's the eagle and all kind of thing,
but it's actually the phoenix with the arrows in it.
The phoenix emulates itself in its nest
and then sets itself on fire and turns to ashes.
Who allegedly works for the Illuminati?
You do, I allegedly do too.
But you know what, it's just like,
the thing about Illuminati is like it's not like a it's like it just it just means you
those who know like and so that there's some that I think so a lot of people do and and so even if
you're not initiated in anything you can technically because Alistair Crowley there was one time he
wrote in a book like a secret that only like a 33rd degree Freemason would know that he wasn't a
33rd degree Freemason because he wrote that secret in the book they initiated him to that because
It's all about the knowledge. It's not necessarily about danger. So too, that's why my brother one of them keeps one of my dad
Said they were gonna make him amazing because you know, I guess it's your family it runs your family
Yeah, we'll be involved with it, right?
Yeah
To like they offer me told her she could be like they're saying how Job's daughters, right?
And he wasn't yeah
so Alistair Crowley was in the Golden Dawn and then he
Basically took over the Golden Dawn. He like by force actually he like broke into the offices and took yeah
Cleared himself the head of it, but then he started something called the OTO, but he's also initiated a Freemasonry in Mexico
Leave that he
He was so decorate him. He had every degree everything and then he basically took the teachings and he put them for his own organization
Yeah, everybody right and he started his yeah, he started the OCO or ordo tempu
Yeah, yeah, I said
A lot of the coal. I don't know. Are you interested in the occult or not or yeah, I don't know too much about it
Yeah, well, I mean it all it all kind of comes together under like it's like are kind of America was founded by
which is like what is really interesting like there's just a lot of meat there's a lot of
secret meaning like everything is symbolic it's a very much about symbolism it's about
real magic but it's also but and the thing about it is there's also like what has turned into a
little bit is um a duality because it is about duality and that's the back of me but it's like saying
The very top are the the sacred and like the gods and then everybody else and you've been hit down on the pyramid is profane
Yeah, it's like and so they all want to see other people like animals or cattle
Which is funny only like we have the locale thing in YouTube, which is like, but um
That's what that's where I don't agree with. I don't agree with dehumanizing humans
Yeah, those and then their gods and stuff like that and because there is a lot of the problem is with ego
Once you give away all these metals and degrees and
Importance and then it's like and then you think you're they get very smug
I think it's kind of gotten a little bit polluted like that. So that's why I'm all cherry
Practitioner I'd like but I but you because you just didn't take oaths along the way and
That that limits what you can talk about. So I like to be able to talk about anything I want because I'm a big mouth
And I'll accidentally give away the secrets if I was yeah, I was sworn to secrecy the mason's day
They'll cut out your throat. Yeah, they're yeah, you're in secrecy or whatever
But he was what what do you call there's two kinds of mason's it was a top one set
Born into it. You're like born into it or something
There's, you know, there's the first three, the first three degrees, like something called the porch masons because they like, they go through like this, like the initial processes and then they're like, they don't want to go any further.
If you can go higher and higher, it depends. And then there's a saying like, you're tested and it's like, I guess they asked you to like, maybe.
This is just a theory where they ask you know either like spit on a spit on a cross or something like that
And if you do it you pass. Yeah, well if you don't do it you pass too, but but they still send you to different parts of parts of masonry, right?
And yeah, you know, they are the architects. They are like builders. I think that they are the artificers also of
history
History is just fake and you know
I think a lot of things are more recent than we think.
And there's the blue lodge, the red lodge,
there's also the checkerboard floor, the black and white.
There are very much about duality,
which is also like taking part in like the blacks and whites,
always being at odds and stuff like that.
And finding it's because...
That's the black versus the white and so they're the most extremely dualities
And so they love to stoke up racial things like oh the George Floyd thing which is a Masonic sigh up
I mean, it's very they do control a lot of the news news
What is the newspaper black and white just like the checkerboard floor, right?
It's like so and what is news news is not news
It's old because it's like because it's not new it's already it's already been done. So is I don't know
Damn, yeah, that's that is kind of interesting. I want to go to bohemian grove because I hear there's a bunch of guys running around naked there
You know Richard Nixon said he said that but he would you would go to bohemian grove because presidents go there
And he said but it was a faggiest goddamn thing he's ever been to he's like. Oh really?
He said Nixon said yeah, it's on it's in the water
Nixon yeah
I remember I was a little kid when he was president.
I remember my mom used to say, he has a face shaped like a potato, the potato face.
Oh yeah.
So I thought of him like, yeah, that's a potato face, man.
I was little though.
It's like, I remember he'd be on the TV news and if he'd watch him because they were all
these diehard Republicans, my dad especially, my mom.
My dad was also Republican, but my dad was you know, we're California Republicans and California Republicans tend to be a little bit more
The the libertarian flavor where we're not so socially. Yeah, correct, you know, but it's more of an economic
Conservatism rather than social conservatism. So it's very different from a southern Republican who are very
Yeah, they're usually religious
Exactly
And so, you know, but yeah, I mean, my dad loved Trump and stuff.
And we used to fight about George W. Bush.
Oh, my mom, my mom couldn't stand Trump, you know, and when he, oh my God, yeah, I mean,
shit.
And then look at him.
He was president.
She used to not like him when he has that, had that TV show or whatever.
Yeah.
She couldn't stand him.
But if you look back in history or like back when, in like the 80s and 90s, Trump was in
Kind of he was I didn't know that he was
He was in he was in a lot of he was in a lot of he was in commercials
He was in because he was more of a celebrity kind of
You know he's like Reagan my mom loved Reagan Reagan was in like he was like in black and white films like a cowboy films
I saw yeah, I saw that yeah, I remember
You know when I first voted when I first voted that's that's who I voted for when I was turned
Born that was he was actually I think Jimmy Carter was coming out of office. I was born in January and so
But it was like but technically it was like Reagan was the first president
You know Nancy Reagan was really into astrology
And she had astrologers that they couldn't do anything, schedule anything without the astrologers giving the check mark okay for it.
They didn't check them.
And so everything was down to like the minute of things sometimes.
She was such a believer in astrology.
And it's really interesting.
I don't know if there's any, yeah, right?
Well, the first president, Reagan,
was the neighbor of my parents in Tanglewood here
in Houston, Tanglewood.
And we'd always see his Barbara,
we'd see her at the movie theaters.
The Secret Service would take her over there,
but she was very friendly with people.
And she went to the Chinese place
that my parents used to go eat at.
They would go there with their Secret Service and eat.
And we'd see her walk in Millie, the dog.
You'd see see them through the gate, but then there were so many people coming from all over
Tourists and they were like crowding the streets to see their place
So they went ahead and shut down that street and it pissed off all the neighbors because you know
They had to go out of their way to get out of there. My mom was pissed
You know, it was like damn, you know, they they closed that road because he's these tourists or whatever they were yeah
Though yeah
Okay, so there's a thought that, you know, Barbara Bush is Alistair Crowley's daughter.
Yeah, Barbara Bush. Yeah. And then if you look at their pictures, they look a lot alike. I got a
lot. Let me see if I can find a picture of them. Yeah, I don't know that other lady that you just
mentioned. Barbara Bush. She was George Bush. No, Barbara Bush. Yeah, I know her. We've seen her.
Alistair, his name was Alistair Crowley. He kind of like was a cultist, um,
very famous occultist. That's kind of like the father of modern rock and roll. He was on the Beatles
Sergeant Pepper album. He, he predicted the new age. He said there's gonna be a lot of sports games
and there's gonna be a lot of entertainment and, and things to distract the masses. And he called it
the age of horrors. Um, but I'll show you their pictures because it was said that he did some kind
in like with and they're put in place and then Barbara Bush looks like just like him. I don't
not sure if it's 100% accurate because it's like never been a DNA test and it's supposed to be his
father but I'll show you this picture of them together. This is a bush connection. This is uh
let me get it okay here we go yeah here is their pictures together and you can see what you think
Don't they don't these people
Look exactly alike here we go
Photos have you seen this sex magic? Yes, he was the point of the here
He was one of the big people into in there you
So that was him and look look I don't see it. I don't see the
No, y'all just see you me on the panel. Hmm. Maybe we'll take a second cuz it's yeah, okay
I don't know if it's like we'll catch up. Are you don't see it? Yeah, no, I'm not seeing I just see you
Hmm, maybe I can also sing I'll see if I can put the link backstage for you here. Okay
Or send it. Do you remember Geraldine Ferrara? Yeah. Yeah, I've forgotten her name
Um, I remember that when she was running for office my mom, you know, because her her
Father was a politician in Bolivia and she was involved, you know with politicians and stuff
But I remember she was in town and Raquel Welch, which is which her dad
Her mom was a Bolivian and her dad was American.
That's why her name, you know, so she invited my mom
because you know, the Bolivians are close or whatever,
even the celebrities.
And it was in Conor that we're having something going on
and Geraldine Ferrara was going, running for office,
I think, for the States, I don't know.
But her son was in the news already
because he got arrested for something,
the drugs or something.
and hello? Oh, okay. So anyway, they went to this convention and Geraldine Ferraro told my mom, she goes, you're so beautiful, like, like, you know, like Raquel Welch and she goes, you guys are exotic looking. And my mom, instead of saying thank you, she's like, oh, your son's all over the news, is he okay? You know, it was like, my dad was mad, he's like, what did you have to bring up?
the son, but the ladies said you're just as beautiful as Raquel Welch, you know, the South Americans are beautiful at Bolivian, she said, but Raquel Welch is half Bolivia like me, her mom was American, and her dad was Bolivian, and that's why she brought a lady from Bolivia that was running for office in Bolivia, and that's why she was running that convention.
We have a guest backstage, I don't know who this is, I'm going to put the banner up real quick.
Hello Rolly, it's probably a fake account. Rolly Rolly you have five seconds four
Three two. Oh you left. Okay, because it's a
Somewhere though, but yeah back. Hold on Rolly Rolly
It's a poem bomber
Hello
Are you here for the drama?
Who are you, Roli?
Are you a fan of?
No, he's not.
He's giving you a hard time.
It's a troll, probably.
He's trying to get away from the drama.
You want the drama?
They want drama.
Well, what I'm going to go ahead and do is I'm going to jump off because I'm going
to get the link for you.
I'm going to text it to you.
Okay. Hello. Good. I'm gonna text it to you. Is Arthur still in your chat?
Arthur if you're still here, I will
So you can send it to him, but don't send it around to everybody. I know I will I'll just send it to him
Yeah, he'll probably see it around but still you know, it's it's I have it private
But I'll I'll open it and I'll go ahead and send you the link and that way you both can see it
Oh, yeah, Arthur here is Arthur. It was me. It was me. Come on now, brother. Oh, hey, Arthur. I thought I thought it was Christine playing trick on me. Yeah, I didn't know before you leave. I am like, I did not know that you were the lady that Zaya was talking about the Bolivian in all that picture.
He doesn't know anything about me because he was trying to defend somebody who took over $2000 from me.
Oh, and if you look at all my videos, you'll see who it is and and her kissing my ass and oh
You're a good person and all this shit
That's why he did it and that's the one that is telling people that she's cooking up with him
So yeah, he went at me because he said he and I were friends at one time. I was never friends with him
Yeah
Yeah, so he's defending her and Peds doesn't know it that he's still talking to that bitch right now
Calling her because he was gonna hook up with her in New York when he went to see
Carissa and I have proof of that too because she texted it to me
So he's a shady piece of shit. I don't like Zaya. He's a gruder, you know
And he's a phony and I have the text of him I even have his message is calling her beautiful and he was going to see her but then when he went to New York he called her in a rage all pissed off say no we're not going to meet you then because she had said something against pebs or something like that it didn't make sense.
Yeah.
So yeah.
Who is Ella like you always talk about her on my yeah, that's her that's her that's her that he's talking to
Behind the scenes and I have texts of her telling me that she has to use
Why is she never in the chat so she ever say
Because she has a lot to hide that's why because the Skelly called her out before and also I have a communication between Skelly and somebody
where he's talking shit about her, saying that Miss Parker and BGTV
came to him to defend her and saying she's suicidal, please take down the videos of her.
I have that communication and I'm going to send it to somebody who asked for it.
That's the s word here. Oh, come on. Yeah. No, I just don't like the shadiness and all this because I don't know these people and
And that one woman scammed me out of money and she and I even posted a
Communication from her ex best friend that told me once you block her she goes nuts on you because she said she had a hard time
Shaking her off, you know, and that's exactly
But yeah, look at all my videos, but Arthur, I gotta get going, but I'm gonna go ahead and make it
You know open that video so you and psyche can see it and then I'm gonna
I'm gonna put it on list. It's only you two could see it
And I'm gonna do that right now because I gotta get ready and get
Yeah, I'll send it to him it by text
And then he can, I don't know if you text with him.
If not, he can send it to you here in chat or whatever.
Thank you.
So I'll send it now.
Okay.
Because, okay.
All right.
You guys have a great day.
Yeah.
You too.
Okay.
Love you too.
It was nice meeting you, Arthur.
You're actually cool.
I was interesting.
Come on.
Can we give a shout out to Bita?
You know, it's wave the white flag in peace.
Well, I wish we could but she's angry too because I'd had Barb talking about her before and
You know because we used to talk sometimes and it's just you know, it's just I don't know
I'll let you see but don't share it because I don't even know what happened because I fell asleep as soon as I started recording. I was exhausted.
I think Bita probably struck it for using her image and stuff like that.
Oh, I didn't know. Like I said, I didn't see it. All I did was I hit record as soon as it started and I got busy and then I forgot and I fell asleep and then I woke up.
Late this morning and I saw that it was recorded in it and that the video was actually removed
But I checked it and I have all of it. It even stopped at the end of it. Yes
Yeah, it automatically records these videos and it'll stop by itself because I thought shit man
Is it still running?
No, this is like crazy because you are like that's like I don't even know how to do that and you're doing that
This is not some kind of like, you know
Senile old woman. This is someone that's in Mary. I know I know a lot of stuff. Yeah, I'm not very bright
She's just mad at me and say because she used to say I'm so intelligent and all tech savvy
And all of a sudden because of my age, and I don't even look like my age
She said yeah, she's mad and you know, I don't even know and I'm not a public figure and what she did is wrong with you know
Just doxing people's names and stuff. So I get
I guess I learned from my brother and I've always had a high, you know, like you know, they tested me as I'm real smart
I'm up there and my brother's kind of considered a genius like my my dad was
Yeah, so I just figured things out. It's easy
No, no, no, no
Is your last name musk is your name next musk
That would make sense because I think one of his
No, I'm all there, but who knows I might get Alzheimer's and when I'm 80 like my dad did
You know
Cuz you just called it all timers. I think it's called all
Alzheimer's I spell with a Z no, but he's
But but you get it because his dad did too, so I might get it
You know at least I don't have the health issues my mom did because she passed away younger than me and I expected
If we can do that long enough, we'll eventually get something.
That's the thing.
And the thing is, it's like I OD'd and took
enough to kill a horse, they said.
And I made it.
Look, I made it.
And here I am for a reason.
And that's why I say you're healthier than a horse.
Very healthy now.
When I got big, though, I was starting
to get diabetes, too, and high blood pressure.
All that's been gone for years.
Yeah, and and and you see me, you know, and you saw the camera and she's she's uh, she's she's walking around
She's very virile and uh, and I'm saying I'm not
Honest, you know, uh, you know Mary J in the chat. I think that's her name Mary J, but she goes under a different name now
I don't know that person. No, what about her marry something? Mm-hmm. What about her? I don't never mind
I thought you knew never mind. No, I don't know what they're talking shit about me or something
No, but I've done some things in the past for somebody, you know, which was stupid and I was doing a lot of drugs
And I don't do those things anymore. Oh
All I do is react on my YouTube. That's it. I don't go real life on people. Are you crazy?
I almost got in trouble a couple years ago and I was never in trouble when in 82. I was in college
So yeah and put all kinds of stuff on you. I know but yeah, I'm appreciate you psyche
So I'm gonna go ahead and unlist and put it unlisted and text it to you. So give it to Arthur. Okay, sounds good
All right, you have a good day you too. Bye-bye. Bye
Here we have a Samman in the chat there's Samman Swallows. What a great name Samman
Red and blue cosine waves. Yeah, so red and blue. Yeah
Red and blue they say on the what are we're red and blue on the American flag and other flags, right?
And also are the primary colors, you know the primaries and
Hey guys, I I'm very I have a very abstract mind. I can't oh here. Yes, sir. There you I'm sorry
How are you drop off and do something?
Yeah, I thought it was you in the chat someone was saying oh take away check
He's mod and someone said it was I said is it CS and they're like yeah CS and I was like
That's why I thought you were in there always blame me for shit, bro. Like I'm not even like
I checked with you. I didn't just do it. I wouldn't like not agree
But I'm saying to the other people like damn, bro. Yeah on my dick
Well, I want to get away from it. I wanted to come on. I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry
Yo, so I mean dude. I and I she left damn it
For you because they didn't take that off tonight, but uh
Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy Roy
Like how does she even know how to screen record that shit is crazy my father
Like he never wanted to use a computer and he until the day he passed away
He had like this ledger like a successful businessman
But he would have like a ledger where he would do all the math by hand for everything and like in this little like ledger book
And stuff, you know, he never he wanted me
computers you want to
What's that Heath Ledger not a Heath Ledger. It was like a Ledger like a little book with like, you know
You just all those black and white notebook ones. Yeah, you know black and white notebook like Anne Franks. Oh, he's a genius man
He well, you know what he was old school. He was an old school kind of guy
He didn't like to have the newest cell phone, but he's
Right, right, right and ready yellow red. That's what is ready? I have a black and yellow ring
Just black, yeah, the yellow sapphire and black, the black one is a haunted ring,
got an Etsy, it still has a spirit in it, but yeah. Oh, I won't get to my spirit keeping.
Suck your balls, you said?
Like my balls. Why would you tell me to do you while it was not safe to say that to me Arthur because I will
No, that was Cartman Cartman for himself. Oh my god
Hey, do you ever see that episode of South Park where like Cartman?
There's a he goes to sleepovers with butters and when butters falls asleep. Oh my god
Take a picture
Yeah, there's like I suck butters dick. I said butters dick when he fell asleep. He's gay
Yeah, you're fucking gay. You suck this dick
What?
Dude, I love South Park.
That shit is hilarious.
Text me the link, Arthur.
So I'll try to get it backstage for you.
You can put it backstage here real quick.
Nobody else will see.
I will, I will.
Hold on a second.
Let me see.
But then you can delete it.
I got it, I got it.
Roy, Roy, Roy.
But yeah, I mean it's like so how's beat I've been treating you and everything like dude man
She is like yesterday. She got drunk. I guess bro. She banned me from the chat. I'm like I didn't do shit
What else she was?
She was accusing me of being racist, but you heard that clip maybe the people want to hear maybe you can play that clip
I heard the clip. I remember she used me to be a racist because I said the end word one time
I mean, it's like geez. I mean, it's like I mean I was saying it
to take the power away from it.
But now, and Alex was buying with it,
and now she's calling me a racist.
I mean, it's ridiculous.
I think the people-
There you go, I got it, thank you sir.
Okay, there you go.
It might have been Nathaniela, is that Nibiru or something?
Nibiru?
I don't know.
Go ahead, Nibiru.
Thank you.
I got it.
I got it, Karen.
Thank you so much.
Am I taking steps to make my channel not?
Yeah, I'm not going to...
No, Brandon Q is not allowed anymore.
We'll have to get an excuse by case basis, you know?
Fucking finally, dude.
There's two cool first schools back.
Hey, what's up?
Hey, there's J-Dog.
What's up, J-Dog?
Oh shit, bring them on panel.
Yeah, you come up if you want, but you know you Jada got put in a video too or it's like oh Jada confirms that psyche's a piece of shit or something like that
Well, it's like so I mean he didn't it was just like when he was on my show like talking cool and stuff
But I don't I don't know Jada guys getting crazy now. She's harassing pray page. You know, pray page. She's harassing pray page now
Be the no Alex
Content
No, but she's trans. Oh, come on. That's what she said. I mean, I mean, it's like so ridiculous. Like, I don't know why she's ever even better.
How she's all that's right. That's a good point. Is that true though? You sure about that? Yeah, that's what she said. But if you're using Tomula Sorter, that's I went to a Dodger game when I was a kid and there's Tomula Sorter right there.
Roy.
It is the real Tomula Sorter. It is. Yeah, I'm looking through his old albums when I see my I can see my grandpa here is my grandpa.
Yeah, and I love my grandma. I love my grandma. Yeah, that was in the
Airport or something. That's me a little kid, huh?
Grandma was a good lady, man. She was a good lady. She was very low and then I had an Aunt Betty
Who took me in South Carolina and his Aunt Betty. Oh, Aunt Betty? I know her.
Oh yeah, this is oh, yeah, so in South Carolina they are north it was we actually drove to North Carolina
There was rock you slide down so sliding. Yeah, I think he's backstage. Okay. Oh, sorry. He's not backstage yet
Oh, okay.
Yo, do you know what song Black Muddy, Black Muddy, Black Muddy, Black Muddy, Black Muddy?
And then I have a cousin named, I think his name is Chris, and he was a bad boy.
He was like a, he has a Who For Him Roger Rabbit T-shirt, and he was like, I'm cool.
And then we played video games all day, like more, like, you know, but look at the TV,
it's like, so like, like, it looks like it was like a thousand years ago, like a 50s.
Right, right, right. Okay. Here we go. Jay dog. Jay diesel my nizzle
Thank you, Arthur. What's up, bro? How you doing this? Oh, how you doing there? Jay diesel chilling chilling
Just getting lit before I got to go to work
What were you talking about Arthur who kicked you off and who was it beta dude beta bro beat is over here fucking
Racist and then you heard that clip. Maybe you want to play that clip for him psyche
Yeah, I'll show you the cover one, I can get backstage and get a real quick call.
So, yeah, this is, um, hold on.
The beat of the clip.
I'll define it almost like I did my history.
It should be in your history.
You guys, you're smart too, man.
History and then, let's see, it was this...
Oh, here it is, I got it.
60-year-old Californian woman is raped.
Listen to this.
Listen to this J-Doc, you'll be shocked.
Okay, here you go. I'm gonna go on you for a minute. Okay. Go on me for a second. Here we go
This is a six-year-old California woman
saying
the n-word
I
Appreciate it. Oh, yeah, Michigan niggas forever. Oh
Lord
He's going the bottom bitch
Samans new super what are you gonna do?
Are you gonna keep there?
I've only heard Saman say that
Don't worry about Saman, you don't have to bring Saman into the room
Your nigger ass doesn't have to bring Saman into the room
Your nigger ass
Saman is gonna...
Saman will always fucking be Saman
And I'm fucking rock with Saman
So what the fuck are you gonna say about Saman?
You fucking bitch
What's your nigger ass in the
middle of your palm?
Scrunch it up and fucking throw it in your mom's face.
Oh my god.
Look at your penis and
wonder why you don't have a nigger
talk. Oh my god.
Oh my goodness.
Oh my lord.
We're doing the nigger challenge tonight nigger.
Stupid fucking Canadian dumb charge. It's a fuck out of here. Jesus Christ man. Look at this
Well, I mean, you don't have to be Jesus Christ in today. This is this thing
Nigger and she's disgusting stop it. Well times
Appreciate it. Oh my god. Oh, yeah
Dude Lord, you still in the bottom bitch. She is nuts
Sam and his new superstores.
What are you going to say? What are you going to do?
That's enough of that.
I want to show you the guys. I found this album
and I put some pictures of Lenore
from like a few years ago and not here.
This is Lenore from a few years ago
and there's here with my cat.
Oh, that was my cat.
Got them at the same day.
Yeah, and he passed away, but unfortunately.
Oh, I'm sorry.
But then I had a cat named Silly.
And I had a cat named Caleb.
You can see Silly and Caleb right there.
There's Silly.
He's a black and white.
That's the one that Coyote's got.
But I love my cats.
And there's Caleb right there.
He lives next door now.
He's a good white cat.
But all three of them are like sleeping in front of the TV.
Boy, there's Kassim Lennon right there.
Kassim Lennon.
He loves her.
They love the licks. They're so cute and oh and I have them I have a picture of my
My room when I was oh, this is kind of cool. I had this. Oh, here's a picture of me and drag
It was me and drag J now. What do you think?
What was that picture
That was in my eighth grade and they had like an opposite date.
So maybe I just-
Oh, okay, okay.
I was like, wait,
cause you look relatively young right there.
I was really, I was really young.
Okay. It was good.
I can see my own pictures.
Yeah. Yeah. It's your own picture.
My own picture.
So it's like, you know,
I know no one's going to do any funny business.
What else?
I have a picture of my bedroom and I was like a teenager.
And, oh, here it is.
You can see I was all into like leopard print
or something like that.
But this is my room when I was a teenager.
My room you see your room was nice and clean. They're trying to say like that
Oh, yeah, it's like he's not gay cuz he ain't a nice clean guy look at his room is all nice in me
I schooled my school was like right on the right on the cliffs and so there
Oh hell yeah, so anyway, and then I don't have one more. I think I'm
like I
Was always into like
the
This is when I went to South Carolina here or here. I had a hair-raising experience, you know
I found here's the ball this electric ball. They drove me all the way to the
Special North Carolina Museum of like science or something that I could touch the static ball
Well, that's the one that makes your hair like go up like for is up. Okay
Yeah, that was fun. So that was that.
Pretty cool.
So she's been making more stuff about you?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, continue really.
Well, because I did that season assist and saying,
don't say my full Google name and then say it PDF.
That's all I said.
Hey, she thought I meant don't say my name at all. So she started saying my mom's name
Um, and that's still doxing dude. That's still the same thing. She's just not doing it to you
She's just giving it to your family members. Yeah
Yo, was that not crazy?
Yeah, yeah, well beta is crazy. Was that last night?
Did she get that last night a lot five six months ago?
Oh, okay. Well good. This bitch does so much crazy shit, dude
It's hard to keep track of when she goes. What crazy because
She's always going some crazy shit, dude. It's like yeah, but my issue is like she banned me for life from a channel
Because I asked her why can people say the n-word and not get banned, but I asked her that question and I get banned
And it's like Gracie and then she she's open like Tracy's are like baby or something like where are the standards to that? She's like
This is to my friend Tracy. Stop it. Don't like that.
Me saying the fucking hard R. It's like what?
Dude she picks and chooses when she wants to follow rules, dude. It's like some people like dude
She got so mad because um, elbow is supposedly upset at her last night because she was um
She allowed a wrongs alter ego to put up supposedly elbows docks picture
I think he's just he's just playing it up. I don't even know if it even if it was his pictures like who cares like like
Why does he care like he did a whole show about beat it and I and put her like witch pictures up and called it like
He had cursed by a witch or something like that. He called it although good there
But you know what?
Yeah, everyone was there, but guess what happened after that what happened a clip came in and like, oh beat it
Alexander wants to speak to you and so I looked at alexander's and guess who's at alexander's
Whoa
And crystal am
You know, they're all friends now. Yeah, they're friends now. They're friends now. They were having a little girl pow out
I mean, it's like fine. It's like, you know, that's good. Like we can get along and stuff, but
Do you we're trying to do that months ago when when when this all happened you were trying to get everybody to get a long
Months ago and she was saying I'll never be her friend again. I will never talk to her
And making all kinds of videos and shit like that. It's like what the heck
Well, then she did a she went live it later because she was responding to me
But you know what she said at the end of her stream she said
And there's this woman, Prairie Page, and she's like,
I think Prairie Page is luring men to her chat
from Psyche's chat, and I think Prairie Page is a trans.
That's what she said.
Oh my god.
You believe that one?
I think, now she's trying to go after Paige, like.
She's opening, she doesn't even know her.
I don't even think she ever talked to her one time.
Not even been on the same panel together, never.
What she's trying to do, she's trying to get people mad
at me, like, blaming me, right?
She's trying to get people that she thinks are like,
good like good people or supporters of them to blame me for her going after them because they
know me and stuff like she even had like a tweet that said you know oh well i'm gonna be people's
manifestation of their worst nightmare against their loved ones and they're gonna blame them
and then wow that sounds like a threat like a motherfucker that was a hell of a threat yeah
and she's actually doing it then it's several people and it's like you know i mean it's like wow
Just leave me alone. I mean it's like I would leave her alone if she was just leaving me alone
All I said was that she was played the mother in the Cosby show porn, but she tells everybody herself
So it's not even a big deal. Oh, she really did like oh
See, I never walked any of her
Yeah, see I don't look at her in that type of way. I
I'm looking at Elsa. Oh, I mean I saw her fuck some guy with a dildo and stuff and oh my god
Oh, no, I never I didn't say I never seen
Yeah, but I just went on to other things.
It was kind of a bit of a vanilla for me.
She never did DP or anything.
She just said like single and vaginal stuff.
See, this is not slander.
This is just the truth.
She got mad at me because once I said she did DP
or something like that, she's like,
that's the only thing on her feeling.
She did not do DP.
She only did one at a time.
I don't know the story why she got kicked out of the industry.
I don't know.
I don't know, there's different stories.
I'm not gonna say it, but I'm not a fucking dick.
Like she's being to me.
i mean she's being just fucking so cool you got to just take the higher roads like i know it's
hard sometimes bro you gotta get out of my place like like like she thinks like that like i'm
gonna kick out because she thinks like the management companies like you know so she's
trying to make you feel essentially she's trying to make you like homeless now trying to physically
cause harm to you so you said she's acting like a dick yeah so i mean she's being nice to you
Arthur, I'm yours.
He's trying to jerk on us.
Technically, I mean, I think-
Because I didn't mean-
I think in your turn it should be she's acting like a pussy.
I didn't mean to hurt her because I'm straight, because I would have met J-Dog
because I want to get fucked, I guess, by J-Dog and I-
Yeah, but you should say she's acting like a pussy because you don't like pussy.
Okay, but I know but now it gets too confusing. Okay, let's just
He's stuck on the wrong part of the story. He's stuck on the wrong
Unistake's armpit, I don't know. I don't know
I don't know.
Okay.
Right.
What?
Hey, guys.
I got a picture of J-Dog in a Mexican wrestler's outfit.
Um, and then.
No, I always thought J-Dog was Indian.
No.
You're going to be like,
Yo, I always thought you were Indian.
No, I'm not a hubby.
It has to be the beard and the the skin tone and a lot of people when I go in the liquor stores
And there every time I go in a liquor store people do you can't start talking to me and prove Javi?
Yeah, oh dude, I was gonna that was what I was gonna tell you um
Dude, I think Paige is asexual. I don't even think she lures men like over to her
Yeah, but every time like somebody hicks on her stuff like that like she's all like weirded out and stuff like that
So I don't think she's up here for anything like that
Yeah, she just wanted to kill yeah
Mac on her
She's a very sweet person, I let her know, and then I kind of like, but it's like,
Who are we talking about now?
Paige.
Ah, yeah, Paige, Paige, uh.
It's a little cuckoo in the head, I ain't gonna lie.
Oh, come on, Arthur, Arthur.
But the thing is, I think Paige is awesome.
Guys, by the way,
Prairie Paige has been doing like lives a lot.
And so I really wanna like support her channel.
So Prairie Paige, Wild Flowers and Arts,
I think it's her, is there a win?
Yeah, I think it's her page.
But go over and say hi to her.
But if she does reading, like, you know,
free readings, she's a great reader.
She call it.
She thinks she says, I'm a great reader too.
But...
Yeah, she's been with the show probably since I began the show start coming here and she's kind of gone to community
Yeah, she met everybody because of you psyche. She's because everybody started here like
Beta started coming over here. I was like everybody was over here in the beginning and that's how everybody started knowing each other
And now everybody knows each other, but nobody comes here anymore
And yeah, that's like they just use you and then like they want to go do their own thing
Or they went to somebody else's channel and just continued over there. Yeah
And it's like, but seriously, I'm happy that people, if you give me another chance, because I would, I made a mistake with the Brandon Q.
I think Brandon Q has horrible mental problems. I don't, I'm not sure about all the PDF stuff, but he's just an asshole.
Yeah, honestly, dude, I'm gonna, I'll be straight up with you, bro. That Brandon Q. shit hurts your, it hurts you a lot, bro.
I'm not even gonna lie, I'm not even gonna sugarcoat.
But nobody else was hurt by it, because, you know, Alexandra...
um supported him and yeah but nobody really fucks with alex though i could let like that
rg who came over here every day saying even saying you know i was doing that he's friends with her
and going in and they're trying to and glazing her all the time yeah but rg's a troll though he's
he's just a troll like he gets okay so
Yeah, I was enlightened about a few things like I was like the Tony situation. I know I know all about the KK
I'm I'm gonna say their full name. I know what the KK organization. I know about the
There's another one too. I know about the 007 shit. Okay. Oh, okay. So you're in the know about a lot of stuff there
I'm only in the know. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Doxy me. They're all in her chat, by the way, right?
Uh-huh
Doxy like really badly dog. Anyway
But you know, I don't put it in family members and house
and then maybe something like that.
Right, right, right.
It is like, in which they do harass sometimes, you know?
And so it's like, so that's like the...
And he's like, oh, I don't do any I'm not gonna call it but she's wanting them to but you know
They're too smart to like fall into her trap. She's
No, no, they don't they won't go after you psyche. Well, has it stopped has any as I don't want to like
Tony on indicted on me six, but you know what it was. He's just the fall person
He's just with everyone blames him this up on him, right? Oh, so he did get in. Oh, I'm sorry game
build Chapin
Yes, I know who he is. Yeah, so he's a blind person
Yeah, he looks like a mole rat a blind mole rat
They sent him over to a groovy Jimmy's house and said oh knock on the door and ask for Gary Coleman
Yeah, I remember that getting
It all killed him right yeah
Yeah, and then they had a guy come to his house looking for a laptop this black guy
I think black I punched him in the fucking head and then there's pictures of him with smearing manure into open wounds on his face
I'm doing black face and they
they tried to do this shit to me last year where they were like oh dance to wild horse or um what's
that song with the horses i forgot the name though but there's a song like the buffalo bill song is
out there they're trying to there's some song about horses or something like that but i don't
remember it was and then and they're like oh you know you're singing to it and i was like you guys
are just i never did another thing like that but but there's people that are like autistic or like
Something like I don't know something is kind of wrong with some of the people. They're not PDFs like cuz it's like they'll say they are the people
The people they'll start to say that's just for doing that
But there's no great charges or anything like that, but yeah, and they basically tortured this guy and also they tortured Tony too
Oh, yeah, yeah, Tony. Look he got when he first came around in the Marty section. He got
brutally like
They put him through the ringer and it's your chin style, right?
They never accept him, nor do they accept him still.
I mean, it's like, because they just like, you know, you know, he looks like, he looks
just like Brandon Q.
You're the thing with Brandon Q, dude, is Brandon Q really is like, like.
Sicko dude like he really does say weird. He's weird. He's really weird
And he says fucking weird ass shit, and I thought it was like some kind of dark sense of humor
But it's like no no that guy that you see that's a reason. So here's what we'll do here. We'll take some advice like this
If you see that really nobody really really even allows the person on the panel
Yeah, don't don't let them around you bro because all it's gonna do there's a reason that there that they're not allowed on other people's
platforms for example like LD and I've been told about other people
Y'all seems and like all these people and it's like I just kind of felt it was weak the allegations and stuff
And nobody really cared at the end people did care about this
But the first person to tell me not to have a mom was Tony and stuff, right? Yeah, so I was being like, you know
rebellious or whatever. But what Brandon ended up doing is making a fake profile and trying
to get modded.
And then yeah, he made that underage profile and then he tried to say that
Underage mod. I was it was him. Yeah. Yeah, I know he tried to play that on me
He tried to say you're an opponent with a under and I go wall effects the case thing you are too Brandon
So
Why are you talking to a 12 year old about I'm going to my chat
Um, and then he didn't have anything to say and then he keeps trying to come on under
Oh, he's like I made your show and he just bought a bunch of bots in here. All he has is his cute army is just a bunch of bots
Yeah, he just pays for shit dude
He just pays for fucking subs and box and shit like you cuz nobody fucks with him. Nobody fucks it, Brandon
I don't even know how he came over here
He's banned from the show now and it's like you know and but you know fortunately
I did meet some good people through him, but you know no one had a problem with anybody else having good times
He's had him on the show and
He had him on a show and he's been on other shows
nobody has a problem with anybody that and even clumsy was on his show tonight and so
it's just oh
I'm hated I'm like and then anybody that's even in my chat
Like beat will call pdf she called ghost of pdf just and ghosts never even met brand
I mean it's that's all i'm tripping out like ghost is not even the farthest thing from a pdf like
And then ghosts have been through they pick on ghosts and bully him too, right?
Yeah
because he said something about like he was like talking to his mom and he's like where's the dog and
he's like oh i was just fucking with the dog you know like oh you said you were fucking the dog
no no they took it out of context you know it's like so silly and it's like and they they stick
to it and it's like because if it's effective i mean it's that's the worst thing and it really
does take the tension away from the real bad things that are happening but in everybody
I mean, if somebody's done something, there's evidence.
Are you really going to say, I love to do this?
Justin, internet people, make your own content.
Don't torture innocent people to make it.
I mean, it's like, that's so...
It's getting kind of sick.
I don't know.
I probably want to be streaming anymore.
You know, oh, there he is.
I think I'm going to be brand new, I don't know.
Yo, it's like, yeah, I got to head out, bro.
I'll hit you up later.
All right, guys, Arthur, peace out, guys.
So Arthur's just your Amina Arthur hi Nolan. What is Nolan saying to me? He says
Golden dawn. I like the case of gold. Oh, it's wrote but Rose. Aren't you Brandon?
Rose you're that you're you're the 12 year old mod that he said I had I told you I'm hiding from Brandon. Okay
We'll come in. Oh, thank God. Oh my god. See
She's obviously an adult because who would be in a chat room at 451 in the morning
What is that picture? Is that a guy in the picture? But it's going on not Brandon. Hold on. Does it look like Brandon?
What is this?
Who does who is that? Oh, there he goes
Okay, guys, hold on
You guys want to hear the thing that is song? I have a thing that is song. I wrote it's called you weird
Okay, so the thing that is was on a show one night with he was on the same man and Sam was like staining is you weird you weird
And he's like, he's like, Sam, you just keep saying, I'm weird.
You weed, you weed.
And so I made a song called, You're Weird.
And it's called The Thing That Is Song.
I'll play it right now.
I wish I had a better,
maybe I'll try to find a picture to fill up, but here's a song.
He's behind the perfect time.
Then starts another pointless argument.
Okay, everyone, like, yeah, this one's facts, not fiction.
No names, if the shoe fits, lace it up.
Yeah, funny how you play judge sitting high on your throne pointing out mistakes while ignoring your own
You preach too wrongs don't make it right then throw another punch every single night
Talking bout moves talking bout grace, but anger had you crossing lines all over the place
Nobody's perfect. I'll say it out loud. I own my mistakes. I ain't hiding in the crowd
I've never done never wish someone did I won't let that poison take over my head
I don't need revenge just to get my fill. I'm building a better me work on yourself and the chaos will cease
Kindness hits hard let the healing be built by the wind you keep crucifying people for every mistake like you never scumbled
Like you never broke faith mirror on the wall. Maybe take a look every chapter ain't the same in your own book
I learned from the darkness instead of trying to run
weakness that strength on display some folks stay bitter while I change my way that judgment. Yeah, she's long gone
when I started moving on no more hate trash to sleep at night the strongest move is to walk in
baggage that was never mine leaving all that bitterness somewhere behind riches then burn one more
down there's enough broken people in every town so before you hit sin trying to ruin the name
adding healing no more flow but feeding the crowd don't have to whisper i can say it out loud the
cycle only somebody let's go i'm planting better seeds and that's the life off
ask yourself before you throw another stone have you cleaned up everything inside your own home
we're all human every one of us falls grace is what catches us not building more preach forgiveness
why you're holding on to hate every choice you make becomes tomorrow's weight if we're really
seeking peace then that cry will be the cost because no one wins when our humanity is lost
i'm building a better finally this world has keeps dragging us deeper in pen and break these chains
Healing takes courage and I'm climbing that hill
You can keep the bitterness, I finally found my peace
And that's the kind of legacy that never will cease
You don't have to like me, you don't have to agree
But if I'm working to become a better person
Maybe it's time you asked yourself, what am I building?
Because the strongest people aren't the ones who keep fighting
The ones brave enough to stop